(Sheldon:)Did you bring a friend?
(Amy:)No.
(Sheldon:)Then as a mental exercise
I invite you
(Sheldon:)to figure out why the two of us
can't play three-person chess.
(Sheldon:)Can you believe this guy?
(Sheldon:)Social protocol does, however,
(Sheldon:)require me to bring you
a hot beverage
(Sheldon:)in your time of need.
(Raj:)No, thank you. I'm fine.
(Sheldon:)It's not optional.
(Sheldon:)We're out of tea.
I hope you like bouillon.
(Raj:)I, uh, I guess you're probably
wondering what's got me down.
(Sheldon:)Actually, I was wondering
(Sheldon:)if I could add
a third new chess piece.
(Sheldon:)How do you think people
would feel about Prince Joey--
(Sheldon:)the king's feeble-minded
but well-meaning cousin?
(Raj:)I'm going to be 30 years old,
(Raj:)and I have no one in my life
to love me.
(Raj:)I'm such a basket case, I can't
even talk to a woman
(Raj:)without having alcohol
in my body.
(Sheldon:)The fun thing about
Prince Joey
(Sheldon:)is every time he moves,
there's a one-in-five chance